eliteclicksmedia.com 2011-07-27

# Privacy | Elite Clicks Media

EliteClicksMedia, LLC, ("EliteClicksMedia"), a Florida Limited Liability Company is wholly committed to ensuring the protection of your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains the data collection and use practices of ELITECLICKSMEDIA and all related websites directly or indirectly owned or registered to ELITECLICKSMEDIA. This does not apply to any third party websites, applications, products or services for which ELITECLICKSMEDIA is not a responsible party.

By choosing to access the EliteClicksMedia site, you are hereby consenting to the information collection and use practices described in and implied in this policy as well as the Acceptable Use Policy and the site"s Publisher Terms and Conditions and Advertiser Terms and Conditions. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY PART OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, THE ACCEPTABLE USE POLICY OR THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS PROVIDED ON THIS SITE, PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO ELITECLICKSMEDIA OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEBSITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.DOING SO IS AN AUTOMATIC VERIFICATION OF YOUR CONSENT AND IS LEGALLY BINDING.

##  Revisions or Additions to Privacy Policy:

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all changes are immediately effective upon posting or propagation. It is the sole responsibility of the user to periodically review this policy for updates and each user is solely responsible to be aware of any changes to this and all posted policies on this website. ELITECLICKSMEDIA does not provide notices of any changes in any manner other than by posting the changes to our website.

##  Information Collection, Propagation and Dissemination practices:

This policy applies to ELITECLICKSMEDIA's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by ELITECLICKSMEDIA on its, (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Websites"), (b) on various third party websites, and (c) to ELITECLICKSMEDIA's other information collection, including the acquiring of customer lists from third parties, or the use of customer lists from third parties. ELITECLICKSMEDIA is in no way responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party websites or applications please review the terms of service and privacy policies of these websites before using.

1\. Collection of Information.

1\. a. Specific Information:

When a user provides information to take advantage of a promotional offer, enter to win a contest or sweepstake, send us an email, or otherwise transmit information through the site, ELITECLICKSMEDIA may collect personally identifiable information provided by you, including, but not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address, social security number, credit card information, and telephone number. In accordance with articles of the patriot act you may also provide us with information that, when combined with personally identifiable information, provides us with a better idea of who you are, including but not limited to your gender, birthday, marital status, and education level (collectively referred to as "personal information"). If you choose to access our website, use our services or purchase our products, we may require you to provide personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the site.

1\. b. Passive Information Collection:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA collects information from users when they voluntarily complete a ELITECLICKSMEDIA survey, order form, or a registration page either online by using the internet, offline by providing this information through the mail, in person or using a telephone. This information may be collected by surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties. This method of collection is collectively known as a "Survey." In such Surveys, ELITECLICKSMEDIA or a third party may ask you to provide personal identifiable information including your name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (this includes cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, social security number, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time. ELITECLICKSMEDIA may also collect such information concerning you from another source and uses that information in combination with information provided from this website. Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and you are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to ELITECLICKSMEDIA or a third party, but you may be able to receive incentives from ELITECLICKSMEDIA or a third party in exchange for providing such information.

1\. c. Third Party List Information:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA may collect information from you when you provide information to a third party and ELITECLICKSMEDIA subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the third party. Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (this includes cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the third party. When acquiring this information, ELITECLICKSMEDIA seeks confirmation from the third party that it has a right to transfer the information to ELITECLICKSMEDIA and that the third party has a right to provide offers from advertisers to you included on the third party list.

1\. d. Ulterior Methods of Collecting Information:

There are other occasions when ELITECLICKSMEDIA obtains information from you including (1) your claiming a prize or seeking to redeem an incentive offered by ELITECLICKSMEDIA or by a third party, (2) your requests for assistance through ELITECLICKSMEDIA's customer service department, and (3) when you voluntarily subscribe to a ELITECLICKSMEDIA service or newsletter.

1\. e. Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Information Collected Using Technology:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA like many large websites uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you with information about you in its database to provide a much smoother and more user friendly experience. ELITECLICKSMEDIA may use other cutting edge and revolutionary sources of information in the future. (a) Cookies: "Cookies" are a feature on your browser software. If enabled, we may use cookies that may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of the pages of this Site. Cookies help us in tracking which of our features appeal the most to you and what content you found the most interesting on past visits. When you visit this site again, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your personal preferences. Cookies may be used to: keep track of the amount of return visits to this site; accumulate and report aggregate data, statistical information on website usage; deliver specific content to you based on your interests or past viewing history; save your password for ease of access to our Site. The user may disable cookies at any time, although the Site may not function as easily for you. User browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or to request a notification when a cookie is set. You may read more about cookies at [http://cookiecentral.com](http://cookiecentral.com/ "http://cookiecentral.com"). In order to use all of the features and functionality that are provided by ELITECLICKSMEDIA's websites, you need to accept cookies. (b) Web Beacons: A web beacon is a programming code that may be used to display an image on a web page, but may also be used to transfer your unique user identification to a database and associate you with previously acquired information in a database. This allows ELITECLICKSMEDIA to track preferred websites you visit to aggregate pertinent data. Web beacons are used to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes to determine products or services you may be interested in. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, ELITECLICKSMEDIA also uses web beacons in most email messages sent to those listed in ELITECLICKSMEDIA's database. (c) IP Addresses: ELITECLICKSMEDIA automatically tracks certain information based upon your behavior on the site. This information may be used to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and greatly improve user experience. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. Your Internet Protocol ("IP") is a unique Internet "address" which is assigned to you by an Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a specific computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by Web servers that collect information about a user's preferred traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages. (d) Computer Profiles: ELITECLICKSMEDIA may also collect and accumulate other data which may be deemed as pertinent to help us understand, improve and analyze the Internet experience of our visitors. For instance, ELITECLICKSMEDIA may passively acquire visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. When you provide us with Personal Identification Information, we are able to use such visitor data to identify you. (e) Data Mining: Data Mining technology may be employed from time to time if used by a Client of ELITECLICKSMEDIA. (f) New Technology: The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly developing. As a result, ELITECLICKSMEDIA strongly encourages individuals to consistently revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of new technology.

1\. f. No Information Intentionally Collected from Children:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 18. If ELITECLICKSMEDIA obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 18, that information will be immediately deleted from its database. Because it does not collect such information, ELITECLICKSMEDIA has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. This complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

1\. g. Credit Card Information:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA may collect credit card numbers and related information when an individual places an order from ELITECLICKSMEDIA to protect customers from fraud. When the credit card information is submitted to ELITECLICKSMEDIA, such information is encrypted and is protected with extremely sophisticated SSL encryption software. ELITECLICKSMEDIA will use the credit card information specifically for processing and completing the purchase transaction, and the credit card information will be disclosed to third parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction.

2\. Use of Individual Information.

The following section describes how ELITECLICKSMEDIA utilizes personal information. The uses explained in these sections may change at any time. ELITECLICKSMEDIA may also expand its use of personal information. ELITECLICKSMEDIA reserves the right to use your personal information to provide commercial promotional offers to individuals or entities through, among other things, email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, banner advertising and package stuffers.

2\. a. Discretion for Usage of Information:

The personal information collected on this site and by third parties will be used to effectively operate the site and to provide the services or carry out the transactions requested or authorized by the user. ELITECLICKSMEDIA may change or expand its use of your personal information at any time. ELITECLICKSMEDIA reserves the right to utilize your personal information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, and other possible uses. ELITECLICKSMEDIA MAY SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE REASON IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION

2\. b. Email:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA uses your personal information to provide promotional offers by email to you. ELITECLICKSMEDIA may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If you wish to end your email subscription from a particular list, you only need to press the unsubscribe button on the mail message template. To unsubscribe from all ELITECLICKSMEDIA's email lists, you must submit your email address at [http://www.EliteClicksMedia.com/unsub.html](http://www.eliteclicksmedia.com/unsub.html "http://www.eliteclicksmedia.com/unsub.html"). Such an unsubscribe request will permanently delete your email from all lists used by ELITECLICKSMEDIA. Because ELITECLICKSMEDIA only sends emails when you have agreed to receive emails from ELITECLICKSMEDIA or you have agreed to receive emails from third parties, statutes requiring certain formatting for unsolicited email are not applicable to email messages sent by ELITECLICKSMEDIA.

2\. c. Profiling and Target Advertising:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA uses your information to make and improve profiles of you and to track your online browsing habits and determine which areas of ELITECLICKSMEDIA's websites are most frequently visited. This information helps ELITECLICKSMEDIA to better understand your interests so that it can target advertising and promotions to you. ELITECLICKSMEDIA may, at its discretion, target advertising by using email, direct mail, telephones, cell phones, and other means of communication to provide promotional offers.

2\. b. Personal Information Storage:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA stores your information in a database on ELITECLICKSMEDIA's servers. Our servers have security measures (such as a firewall) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under ELITECLICKSMEDIA's control. Notwithstanding such measures, ELITECLICKSMEDIA cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent ELITECLICKSMEDIA computers from being illegally accessed, and your information from being stolen or altered.

3\. a. Sale or Transfer to Third Parties:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA MAY SELL OR TRANSFER YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY PURPOSE IN ELITECLICKSMEDIA'S SOLE DISCRETION. ELITECLICKSMEDIA uses your personal information in the following ways which may change at any time: Improving Customer Service; Relevant Marketing; and to comply with laws.

3\. b. Improving Customer Service:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA will utilize personal information to reply to you, to process, validate requests or purchase orders, to fulfill any of your requests and to improve over all user experience.

3\. c. Relevant Marketing:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA will utilize your personal information for any marketing and survey purpose on behalf of ELITECLICKSMEDIA and its affiliates and subsidiaries to send information to you about additional goods or services that may be of interest or benefit to you. In addition, ELITECLICKSMEDIA will disclose your personal information to third party agents and independent contractors to assist us conduct our marketing and survey efforts and to share with other companies in connection with marketing efforts including but not limited to direct marketing. You may have no relationship with these other companies.

3\. d. Complying with Legal Process:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA may use or disclose your personal information in response to subpoenas, court orders, warrants, or legal process, or to otherwise establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or in the event you violate or breach an agreement with ELITECLICKSMEDIA. ELITECLICKSMEDIA will use and disclose your personal information if we believe you will harm the property or rights of ELITECLICKSMEDIA, its owners, or those of ELITECLICKSMEDIA's other customers. Finally, we will use or disclose your personal information if we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical or psychological safety of any person, violations of ELITECLICKSMEDIA's acceptable use policy, or as otherwise required by law when responding to subpoenas, court orders and other legal processes deemed relevant.

3\. e. Fulfillment of Orders:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA will transfer your personal information to third parties when necessary to provide a product or service that you order from such third party while using ELITECLICKSMEDIA's websites or when responding to offers provided by ELITECLICKSMEDIA.

3\. f. Summary of Data Processes:

ELITECLICKSMEDIA reserves the right to sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.

3\. g. Random Access to Personal Information:

Users may request access to your personal information that has been collected. You may correct, amend, or delete such information in accordance with legal statutes. You may do this by contacting

This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it

ELITECLICKSMEDIA may also give advertising clients and email services providers' access to your email address to verify the origin of the personal information collected.

4\. Privacy Practices of Third Parties.

4\. a. Advertiser cookies and web beacons:

Third party advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place advertisements on the websites and on the internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technology to collect information about individuals. ELITECLICKSMEDIA does not control the use of such technology and ELITECLICKSMEDIA has no responsibility whatsoever for the use of such technology to gather information about you.

4\. b. Use of Links:

The websites and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of third parties. ELITECLICKSMEDIA is in no way responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other third party websites and will not be held responsible for any transactions or agreements on third party sites. Linked websites may contain links to websites maintained by third parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. ELITECLICKSMEDIA does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such third party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any promotion of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization or partnerships.

5\. Procedures for Unsubscribing.

If at any time you wish to discontinue receiving email messages from ELITECLICKSMEDIA, you may:

(a) Unsubscribe from one email list. To unsubscribe from a particular list, either (1) submit your email address at [http://www.EliteClicksMedia.com/unsub.html](http://www.eliteclicksmedia.com/unsub.html "http://www.eliteclicksmedia.com/unsub.html") or (2) follow the instructions in each promotional email message sent by ELITECLICKSMEDIA.

(b) To unsubscribe from all of EliteClicksMedia email lists.

You may submit your email address at [http://www.EliteClicksMedia.com/unsub.html](http://www.eliteclicksmedia.com/unsub.html "http://www.eliteclicksmedia.com/unsub.html") or write us at:

##  EliteClicksMedia LLC

125 E. Merritt Island Cswy. Suite 209 #330  
Merritt Island, FL 32952

For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).

If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at

This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it
